# (肩座椅)
(Shoulder Seat)
# 作为男人，有时候就要肩负起整个家庭
As men, we need to carry our families on our shoulders sometimes
# 扛起你的爱人或你的孩子
Like your wife and kids
# 但是说直接扛的话会特别疼
But it can hurt if you carry them directly
# 他们会情不自禁地揪你的头发
They will pull your hair sometimes
# 所以说我做了一个肩坐椅
So I made a shoulder seat
# 就是这个
Ta-da
# 纯手工，量身定做
Hand crafted and customized
# 使它像一副铠甲一样穿在身上
Worn like an armor
# 你不会感到一丝不适
No discomfort at all
# 反而会给你带来许多男儿阳刚之气
On the contrary, it really boosts your manhood
# 靠背还有扶手的设计
The designed seatback and armrest
# 让坐在肩上的人更加安全，更加舒适
Offers safety and comfort to users sitting on it
# 也解决了他情不自禁薅你头发的问题
And it prevents them from pulling your hair
# (静静帽)
（Alone Hat）
# 过度的劳累巨大的压力
Life comes with struggling hard work and huge pressures
# 还有生活中大大小小的烦心事
Not to mention all sorts of trouble
# 每当我们面对它们的时候
Every time they hit
# 都想找一个地方静一静
We just want to be alone somewhere and calm down
# 但是说这个能让我们静一静的地方
However, the places for us to be alone
# 却非常少
Are really limited and few
# 有时候还经常会被人打扰
And we get disturbed too often at those few places
# 所以说这几天
So these days
# 通过研究
After some research
# 我做了一个静静帽
I made an alone hat
# 戴上它之后跟我们普通穿的连帽衫外观差不多
The appearance of it is very similar to a hoodie
# 也不会给我们的生活和工作带来不便
Doesn’t bother our life or work
# 当你想静静的时候
When you want to be alone
# 只需要把这个拉下来就行
Just pull this cover down
# 它能快速的给你一个安静封闭的空间
It quickly offers you a quiet and close space
# 不受时间地点和空间的约束
Anytime and anywhere you want
# 当你玩手机，想静静的时候
When you are checking your phone and want to be alone
# 当你上厕所，想静静的时候
When you are in the bathroom and want to be alone
# 当你骑自行车，想静静的时候
When you are bicycling and want to be alone
# 它能让你想静静，就能够静静
It gives you the space to be alone, whenever you want
# 静的快速，静的彻底
Quickly and completely
# (龙头烤串)
(Dragon Head Grill)
# 快要夏天了，大家都喜欢去外边吃点烧烤
Almost summer down here, everybody enjoys a barbecue outside
# 喝点啤酒
Maybe a couple of beers with it
# 我认为自己做
I enjoy having a barbecue myself
# 才能真正体会到烧烤的乐趣
So that I can have the real fun of a barbecue
# 为了让烧烤的过程更加有趣和炫酷
To make the barbecue extra fun and cool
# 我准备做一个龙头烧烤器
I’m going to make a dragon head grill
# 这台龙头烤肉器外观炫酷
It looks zazzy
# 操作方便
And it’s easy to operate
# （危险操作请勿模仿）
(Dangerous, don’t copy)
# 烤串儿
Kabobs!
# 站着烤累了之后
If you are tired standing
# 还可以躺着烤
You can also lie down with it
# 而且我做的这款龙头圣器
Also, this dragon head grill
# 已经在龙之怒吼手游里了
Is in the app game called “Roar of dragons”
# 在游戏里你也可以带上这款炫酷的龙头
You can wear it in the game too
# 去烤一些小龙虾啊，考一些串儿之类的
You can grill some crayfish and kabobs
# 在游戏里还有其他各式各样炫酷的龙
There are also other sorts of dragons in the game, too
# 我做的这款官方说也会送给大家
The app announced that this dragon head grill will be offered to you guys
# 大家可以去看一看
Go check it out